Guide to the George Borchardt Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
George Borchardt Records,
1951-1986
Borchardt, Georges.
176 linear ft (ca. 225,000 items in 423 boxes).
Columbia University Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Butler Library, New York, N.Y. 10027.
4078396
History
Georges Borchardt, a literary agent, began representing French publishing firms in New York during the early 1950s. Later, he also acted for individual French authors who were seeking American publication. Eventually he handled American and English authors as well. With his wife, Anne Bolton Borchordt, he formed Borchardt, Inc. Literary Agency in 1968. His clients have included Flammarion, Gallimard, Denoël, Albert Camus, Jean Giraudoux, Julien Green, Jean-Paul Sartre, Stanley Elkin, and Elie Wiesel.
Scope and Content
Correspondence, memoranda, reports, royalty statements, literary manuscripts and contracts. Among the cataloged correspondents are: Hervʹe Bazin, Laurent de Brunhoff, Michel Butor, Marguerite Duras, John Gardner, Meyer Levin, and Pierre Mendès-France.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into 10 series:
Cataloged Correspondence and Manuscripts
Series I
Series II
Series III
Series IV
Series V: 1957-1984
Series VI: 1971-1986
Series VII
Series VIII
Series IX
Subjects
Georges Borchardt, Inc.; Borchardt, Anne Bolton.; Bazin, Hervé, 1911-1996.; Brunhoff, Laurent de, 1925-; Butor, Michel.; Duras, Marguerite.; Gardner, John, 1933-1982.; Levin, Meyer, 1905-1981.; Mendès France, Pierre, 1907-1982.; French literature--20th century.; Authors, French--20th century.; Authors, English--20th century.; Authors, American.; Contracts.; Literary agents
Access Restrictions
The following boxes are located off-site: 1-419. You will need to request this material from the Rare Book and Manuscript Library at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
Permission of Georges Borchardt, Inc. required to examine or photocopy materials.
Acquisition
1985 Papers Borchardt, Georges gift
1987 addition: Author agency, and publisher files containing correspondence, contracts, offerings, and royalty statements. English language authors and publishers, 1970-1983. French and other foreign language authors and publishers, 1951-1980. Borchardt, Georges Gift
1989 addition: Includes all series described in 1987 addition covering the years 1957-1984, Series V (D-Coll-1); covering the years 1971-1986, Series VI (D-Coll-1) Borchardt, Georges Gift
Gift of Georges Borchardt, 1985-1990.
- Cataloged Correspondence and Manuscripts
  - Allen, Don M. (Box A)
  - Apollinaire, Jacqueline Kolb (Mme Guillaume) (Box A)
  - Ashbery, John (Box A)
  - Bazin, Herve (Box A)
  - Bentley, Eric Russell (Box A)
  - Brunhoff, Laurent de (Box A)
  - Butor, Michel Marie François (Box A)
  - Carroll, Paul (Box A)
  - Codrescu, Andrei (Box A)
  - Crosby, Caresse (Box A)
  - Duras, Marguerite (Box A)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence (Box A)
  - Gardner, John (Box B)
  - Levin, Meyer (Box C)
  - McCarthy, Mary (Box D)
  - Mendes France, Pierre (Box D)
  - Merwin, William Stanley (Box D)
  - Michaux, Henri (Box D)
  - Nin, Anais (Box D)
  - Rendell, Ruth (Box D)
  - Sillitoe, Alan (Box D)
  - Simpson, Louis (Box D)
  - Swados, Harvey (Box D)
  - Troyat, Henri (Box D)
  - Yonrcenar, Marguerite (Box D)
- Series I
  - English Language Authors
    - Alter, Robert (Box 1)
    - Amosoff, Nikolai Mikhailovich & George St. George (Box 1)
    - Andrews, Allen (Box 1)
    - Andrews, Richard M. (Box 1)
    - Astrachan, Anthony (Box 1)
    - Aukema, Charles (Box 1)
    - Azrin, Nathan & Richard M. Foxx (Box 1)
    - Bail, Jay (Box 2)
    - Beiser, Arthur & Germaine (Box 2)
    - Benedikt, Marianne Sabados & Irene Skolnick (Box 2)
    - Benedikt, Michael (Box 3)
    - Benedikt, Michael (2) (Box 4)
    - Benson, Dennis C. (Box 4)
    - Berman, Marshall (Box 4)
    - Billington, James H. (Box 4)
    - Botsford, Keith (Box 5)
    - Bowers, John (Box 5)
    - Bright, John (Box 5)
    - Brown, Doris (Box 5)
    - Brown, Frederick (Box 5)
    - Burland, Brian Berkeley (Box 5)
    - Chambers, George (Box 6)
    - Chapin, Anthony (Box 6)
    - Chester, Alfred (Box 6)
    - Cohen, Arthur A. (Box 6)
    - Cohen, Geula (Box 7)
    - Collier, Peter (Box 7)
    - Coover, Robert (1) (Box 7)
    - Coover, Robert (2) (Box 8)
    - Crombie, John (Box 8)
    - Cruz, Victor Hernandez (Box 8)
    - Dambekelis, Elsie (Box 8)
    - Dawidowicz, Lucy S. (Box 8)
    - Dennison, George (Box 8)
    - Diamond, Stanley (Box 8)
    - Dickstein, Morris (Box 8)
    - Drexler, Rosalyn (Box 9)
    - Elkin, Stanley (Box 9)
    - Elliott, George P. (1) (Box 9)
    - Elliott, George P. (2) (Box 10)
    - Epstein, Joseph (Box 10)
    - Fackenheim, Emil L. (1) (Box 10)
    - Fackenheim, Emil L. (2) (Box 11)
    - Fagles, Robert (Box 11)
    - Feakes, Gordon J. (Box 11)
    - Fleischmann, Glen (Box 11)
    - Flender, Harold (Box 12)
    - Freedman, Ralph (Box 12)
    - Friedman, Maurice (1) (Box 12)
    - Friedman, Maurice (2) (Box 13)
    - Friedman, Paul (Box 13)
    - Friedman, Sanford (Box 13)
    - Gaby, Dan (Box 13)
    - Gallant, Mavis (Box 14)
    - Gamez, Tana de (Box 14)
    - Gardner, John (1) (Box 14)
    - Gardner, John (2) (Box 15)
    - Geissbuhler, Elisabeth (Box 15)
    - Genauer, Emily (Box 15)
    - Ghnassia, Maurice (Box 15)
    - Gloag, John (Box 15)
    - Gloag, Julian (1) (Box 16)
    - Gloag, Julian (2) (Box 17)
    - Gold, Ivan (Box 17)
    - Goldbeck, Nikki & David (Box 17)
    - Goldberg, Gerald Jay (Box 17)
    - Gouri, Haim (Box 17)
    - Haight, Frederick Everest, II (Box 18)
    - Hallo, William W. (Box 18)
    - Hanley, William (Box 18)
    - Harris, Eleanor (Box 18)
    - Hassan, Sana (Box 18)
    - Havas, Laslo (Box 18)
    - Henderson, David (Box 19)
    - Hitchcock, George (Box 19)
    - Holst, Spencer (Box 19)
    - Horowitz, David (Box 19)
    - Huxtable, Ada Louise (Box 19)
    - Israel, Peter (J. Leon Israel, Jr.) "B.F. Cage" (Box 20)
    - Jacoby, Susan (Box 20)
    - Janeway, William H. (Box 20)
    - Johnson, Charles R. (Box 21)
    - Jordania, Redjeb (Box 21)
    - Katz, Steve (Box 21)
    - Karp, Lila (Box 21)
    - Keeley, Edmund (Box 21)
    - Keene, Donald L. (Box 21)
    - Kindel, Stephen (Box 22)
    - Knowler, John "Bruno Wells" (Box 22)
    - Knowles, Roderic (Box 22)
    - Kramer, Hilton (Box 22)
    - Kuhns, William (Box 23)
    - Landon, Howard Chandler Robbins (Box 23)
    - Lawner, Lynne (Box 23)
    - Lecler, Rene (Box 23)
    - Lelchuk, Alan (Box 24)
    - Lendvai, Paul (Box 24)
    - Levin, Meyer (Box 25)
    - Levine, Morton H. (Box 25)
    - Lieberman, Herbert (l) (Box 25)
    - Liebernan, Herbert (2) (Box 26)
    - Lieberman, Jethro Koller (Box 26)
    - Lieberman, Judith (Box 26)
    - Logan, Elizabeth D. (Box 27)
    - Lowery, Bruce (Box 27)
    - Luisi, Billie (Box 27)
    - McElroy, Joseph P. (Box 27)
    - Mainwaring, Marion (Box 28)
    - Malone, John (Box 28)
    - Maloney, David (Box 28)
    - Martin, Todd (Box 28)
    - Marx, Rudolph (Box 28)
    - Mekas, Jonas (Box 29)
    - Miller, William Robert (Box 29)
    - Millett, Kate (Box 29)
    - Molinaro, Ursule (Box 30)
    - Moorse, George (Box 31)
    - Morris, Ivan (Box 31)
    - Mossinsohn, Igal (Box 31)
    - Neuburg, Paul (Box 31)
    - Pauker, John (Box 32)
    - Peacock, Jere (Box 32)
    - Perera, Victor (Box 32)
    - Piquet, Elise (Mrs Julian Gloag) (Box 32)
    - Price, Jonathan (Box 32)
    - Rabinowitz, Dorothy (Box 32)
    - Reck, Michael (Box 33)
    - Reid, Randall (Box 33)
    - Rose, Barbara (Box 33)
    - Rosner, Joseph (Box 33)
    - Richardson, Vokes (Box 33)
    - Robinson, Jeremy (Box 33)
    - Rubenstein, Richard L. (Box 34)
    - Russell, Alfred (Box 34)
    - St. George, George (Box 35)
    - Sanders, Ronald (Box 36)
    - Schaefer, Leah Cahan (Box 36)
    - Schneider, Pierre (Box 36)
    - Sela, Owen (Box 36)
    - Schwartz, Paul Waldo (Box 36)
    - Scott Stokes, Henry J.M. (Box 36)
    - Shapiro, Barry M (Box 37)
    - Shapiro, Sidney (Box 37)
    - Siegel, Jules (Box 37)
    - Sillitoe, Alan (Box 37)
    - Sitney, P. Adams (Box 37)
    - Skedgell, Marian (Box 37)
    - Skillman, Maude (Box 37)
    - Solomon, Barbara Probst (Box 37)
    - Southworth, Herbert R. & Jose Martinez (Box 37)
    - Steiner, George (1) (Box 38)
    - Steiner, George (2) (Box 39)
    - Stephens, Michael Gregory (Box 40)
    - Suvin, Darko R. (Box 40)
    - Swados, Harvey (Box 40)
    - Taube, Lester S. "Ursula Taube" (Box 40)
    - Taubes, Susan Feldmann (Box 40)
    - Teveth, Shabtai (Box 40)
    - Thomas, Audrey Grace Callahan (1) (Box 40)
    - Thomas, Audrey Grace Callahan (2) (Box 41)
    - Tierney, John (Box 41)
    - Torres, Tereska (Mrs Meyer Levin) (Box 41)
    - Valliere, James T. (Box 42)
    - Van Peebles, Melvin (Box 42)
    - Vincent, Peter (Box 42)
    - Ward, Robert (Box 42)
    - Webb, Charles Graham (Box 42)
    - Wiesel, Elie (l) (Box 42)
    - Wiesel, Elie (2) (Box 43)
    - Wiesel, Elie (3) (Box 44)
    - Wright, Richard B. (Box 45)
    - Young, Peter B. (Box 45)
    - Yurick, Sol (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous authors, 1960-1963 (Box 46)
    - American magazines - general (Box 46)
    - American publishers - general (Box 46)
    - Bailey Brothers & Swinfen (Box 46)
    - Ernest Benn Limited (Box 46)
    - Geoffrey Bles Ltd. (Box 47)
    - British agents (Box 47)
    - British publishers - general (Box 47)
    - Burns & Oates Ltd (Box 47)
    - Chapman & Hall (Box 47)
    - Contests (Box 47)
    - The Cresset Press Limited (Box 47)
    - Toby Eady Associates Limited (Box 47)
    - W. Foulsham & Co. Ltd. (Box 47)
    - Galley Press Ltd (Box 47)
    - Hale, Robert (Box 47)
    - Hollis & Carter (Box 47)
    - Inquiries, 1962-1963 (Box 47)
    - New Literature Limited (Box 48)
    - Publishers for Peace (Box 48)
    - George Ronald, Publisher (Box 48)
    - Routledge & Kegan Paul (Box 48)
    - The Ryerson Press Toronto (Box 48)
    - Scorpion Press (Box 48)
    - Neville Spearman Ltd. (Box 48)
    - Weidenfeld & Nicolson, Ltd. (Box 48)
  - French Language Authors and Publisher
    - Abbaye de Saint-Andre Bruges (Box 49)
    - Monastere Saint-Andre de Clerlande, Ottignies, Belg. (Box 49)
    - Alexandrov, Victor (Box 49)
    - Ami, Georges (Georges J. Tardy) (Box 49)
    - Editions Arthaud B. Arthaud Librairie (Grenoble) (Box 49)
    - Aub, Max (Box 49)
    - Aubier Editions Montaigne Editions Aubier Montaigne (1) (Box 49)
    - Aubier Editions Montaigne Editions Aubier Montaigne (2) (Box 50)
    - Audibert, Jacques (Box 50)
    - Bazin, Herve (Box 50)
    - Besterman, Theodore (Box 50)
    - Blais, Marie-Claire (1) (Box 50)
    - Blais, Marie-Claire (2) (Box 51)
    - Blaisdell Publishing Company, New York (Box 51)
    - Bree, Germaine (Box 51)
    - Brunhoff, Laurent de (Box 51)
    - Editions Buchet/Chastel (Box 51)
    - Butor, Michel (Box 51)
    - Editions Calmann-Levy (Box 52)
    - Casterman S.A. Editeurs, (Tournai, Belg.) (Box 52)
    - Cendrars, Blaise (Box 52)
    - Editions du Centurion (Box 52)
    - Les Editions du Cerf (Box 52)
    - Cesaire, Aime (Box 52)
    - Editions Champ Libre (Box 53)
    - Chauvet, Marie (Box 53)
    - Choisy, Maryse (Box 53)
    - Bureau Litteraire D. Clairouin (Box 53)
    - Cocciolo, Carlo (Box 53)
    - Librairie Armand Colin (Box 53)
    - Colin, Rosica [author's agent] (Box 54)
    - Copi (Box 54)
    - Editions Correa & Cie Buchet/Chastel (Box 54)
    - Courtine, Robert J. "La Reyniere" (Box 54)
    - Criterion Books, Inc. (Box 54)
    - Daniel, Jean (Box 54)
    - Danielou, Jean Guenole Louis Marie (Box 54)
    - Daninos, Pierre (Box 54)
    - Delpire Editeur (Box 55)
    - Les Editions Denoël (1) (Box 55)
    - Les Editions Denoel (2) (Box 56)
    - Les Editions Denoël (3) (Box 57)
    - Editions Desclee de Brouwer S.A. DDB (Brussels) (1) (Box 57)
    - Editions Desclee de Brouwer S.A. (2) (Box 58)
    - Dommergues, Pierre (Box 58)
    - Duras, Marguerite (Box 58)
    - Evergreen Review Reader (Box 58)
    - L'Express (1) (Box 58)
    - L'Express (2) (Box 59)
    - Librairie Artheme Fayard (Box 59)
    - Ferro, Marc (Box 59)
    - Flammarion et Cie Librairie Ernest Flammarion (1) (Box 59)
    - Flaminarion et Cie Librairie Ernest Flammarion (2) (Box 60)
    - Editions Fleuve Noir (Box 60)
    - Editions France-Empire (Box 60)
    - Friedlander Saul (Box 60)
    - Editions Gallimard, 1965-1967 (Box 60)
    - Editions Gallimard (2), 1967-1970 (Box 61)
    - Editions Gallimard (3), 1970-1973 (Box 62)
    - Editions Gallimard (4), 1974 (Box 63)
    - Gallimard Anthology of plays (Box 63)
    - Gallimard Aron, Raymond (Box 63)
    - Gallimard Breton, Andre (Box 63)
    - Gallimard Camus, Albert (Box 63)
    - Gallimard Gascar, Pierre (Box 63)
    - Gallimard Grenier, Roger (Box 64)
    - Gallimard Jarlot, Gerard (Box 64)
    - Gallimard Kessel, Joseph (Box 64)
    - Gallimard Lange, Monique (Box 64)
    - Gallimard LeClezio, Jean (Box 64)
    - Gallimard Mendes France, P. (Box 64)
    - Gallimard NRF (Box 64)
    - Gallimard Perret, Jacques (Box 64)
    - Gallimard Pleiade series (Box 64)
    - Gallimard Renard, Jules (Box 64)
    - Gallimard Riviere, Jacques (Box 64)
    - Gallimard Roy, Jules (Box 64)
    - Gallimard Sartre, Jean Paul (Box 65)
    - Gallimard Schehade, Georges (Box 65)
    - Gallimard Serguine, Jacques (Box 65)
    - Gallimard Terray, Lionel (Box 65)
    - Gallimard Textbooks (Box 65)
    - Gallimard Vailland, Roger (Box 65)
    - Gallimard Weil, Simone (Box 65)
    - Librairie Gedalge (Box 65)
    - Ghnassia, Patrick (Box 65)
    - Girard, Andre (Box 65)
    - Giraud, Josette (Box 65)
    - Goetz, Walter (Box 65)
    - Editions Gonthier Editions d'Art Gonthier (Box 65)
    - Goytisolo, Luis (Box 65)
    - Editions Bernard Grasset, 1953-1958 (Box 65)
    - Editions Bernard Grasset (2), 1959-1972 (Box 66)
    - Editions Bernard Grasset (3), 1972 (Box 67)
    - Grasset: Baudelaire, Charles (Box 67)
    - Grasset: Bazin, Herve (Box 67)
    - Grasset: Beaufre, Andre (Box 67)
    - Grasset: Berg, Marina de (Box 67)
    - Grasset: Danielou, Jean Guenole Louis M. (Box 67)
    - Grasset: Gennari, Genevieve (Box 67)
    - Grasset: Giraudoux, Jean (Box 67)
    - Grasset: Green, Julien (Box 67)
    - Grasset: Haedrich, Marcel (Box 67)
    - Grasset: Isaac, Jules (Box 67)
    - Grasset: Ligneris, Françoise des (Box 67)
    - Grasset Martinerie, Andree (4) (Box 68)
    - Grasset: Mauriac, François (Box 68)
    - Grasset: Michel, Henri (Box 68)
    - Grasset: Obaldia, Rene de (Box 68)
    - Grasset: Radiguet, Raymond (Box 68)
    - Grasset: Rochefort, Christiane (Box 68)
    - Grasset: Schakovskoy, Zinaida (Mme de Malewsky "Jacques Croise") (Box 68)
    - Grasset Tatu, Michel (Box 68)
    - Guicharnaud, Jacques (Box 68)
    - Guth, Paul (Box 68)
    - Librairie Hachette (1), 1959-1962 (Box 68)
    - Hachette: Bremond d'Ars, Yvonne Anne-Marie de (Box 69)
    - Hachette: Daninos, Pierre (Box 69)
    - Hachette: Guillot, Rene (Box 69)
    - Hachette: Mireaux, Emile (Box 69)
    - Hachette: Perruchot, Henri (Box 69)
    - Hachette: Vie Quotidienne Series (Box 69)
    - Editions Pierre Horay (Box 70)
    - Julliard-Laffont-Horay Rene Julliard Editeur; Editions Robert Laffont, 1953-1961 (1) (Box 70)
    - Julliard 1962 (2) (Box 71)
    - Julliard: Beau, Georges (Box 71)
    - Julliard: Brenner, Jacques (Box 71)
    - Julliard: Carriere, Jean-Claude (Box 71)
    - Julliard: Curvers, Alexis (Box 71)
    - Julliard: Deak, E. & S. (Box 71)
    - Julliard: Mendes-France, Pierre (Box 71)
    - Julliard: Moury, Alain (Box 71)
    - Julliard: Rostand, Jean (Box 71)
    - Julliard: Roy, Jules (Box 71)
    - Kessel, Joseph (Box 71)
    - Editions Robert Laffont: Conte, Arthur (Box 72)
    - Editions Robert Laffont: Lelong, Maurice (Box 72)
    - La Gorce, Paul-Marie de (Box 72)
    - Lapautre, Michelle Agent Litteraire (Box 72)
    - Lepp, Ignace (Box 72)
    - Mandiargues, Andre Pieyre de (Box 72)
    - Marabini, Jean (Box 72)
    - Matias (Charles Henrioud) (Box 72)
    - Matute, Ana Matia (Box 72)
    - Mauriac, Francois (Box 73)
    - Mende, Tibor (Box 73)
    - Meridian Books, Inc. (Box 73)
    - Monteilhet, Hubert (Box 73)
    - Pirenne, Jacques (Box 73)
- Series II
  - English Language Authors
    - Bailey, Paul (Box 74)
    - Jones, Dennis Feltham (Box 74)
    - Lecler, Rene (Box 74)
    - Mainwaring, Marion (Box 74)
    - Pinner, Erna (Box 74)
    - Piquet, Elise (Box 74)
    - Pollini, Francis (Box 74)
    - Rao, Raja (Box 75)
    - Thackeray, Alec (Box 75)
    - Wiesel Elie (Box 75)
  - English Language Publishers and Agents
    - Aldor, Wilhelm (Box 75)
    - George Allen & Unwin Ltd. (Box 75)
    - Appetron Press Limited (Box 75)
    - Stephen Aske Ltd Literary Ageney (Box 75)
    - Arthur Barker Ltd.: Edmund Burke (Box 75)
    - Arthur Barker Ltd.: Leonard Gribble (Box 75)
    - Barrie & Jenkins Ltd -- Barrie & Rockliff -- Barrie Books Ltd. -- The Cresset Press -- Herbert Jenkins -- Hammond Hammond, 1972-1974 (Box 76)
    - Barrie & Jenkins, 1975-1977 (Box 77)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Agate, James Evershed (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Arms & armor series (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Barber, Richard (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Barford, Philip (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Barrett-Ayers, Reginald (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Baskett, John (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Bell, Colin & Rose (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Bickerton, L. M. (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Blackmore, H. L. (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Boetie, Dugmore (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Branson, David (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Brice, Douglas (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Brodrick, Alan Houghton (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Buchan, Tom (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Carswell, John (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Chaudhuri, Nirad C. (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Cheiro (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Chukovskaya, Lydia (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Church music series (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Collins, Henry & Chimen Abramsky (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Collins, H.P. (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Cooper, Martin (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Crowther, J.G. (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Danielou, Alain (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Darty, Peter (Box 78)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Davies, David (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Davies, Laurence (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Dennys, Rodney (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Edwards, Harry (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Farga, Franz (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Field, P.J.C. (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Finch, Karen & Greta Putnam (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Fitzgerald, C.P. (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Flamant, Maurice & Jeanne Singer-Kerel (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Fowler, John & John Cornforth (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Fuller, John (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Gallet, Michael (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: German literature series (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Ghost books (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Glasfurd, Alec (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Godden, Geoffrey (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Graham, Chive & Bill Curling (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Green, Hugh & John Spencer (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Harrisson, Martin & Bill Waters (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Hiebeler, Toni (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Hotteterre le Romain, Jacques (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Howard, Patricia (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Hughes, John (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Hugill, Stan (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Illustrated guides to pottery & porcelain (Box 79)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Jewish Annual (Explorations). (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Jewitt, Llewellynn Frederick William (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Joseph, Stephen (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Keller, Hermann (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Kenyon, Kathleen (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Kerr, Robert, pseud. (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Knox, Brian (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Kodaly, Zoltan (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Larney, Judith (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Lauder, Ian Paton (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Lenzen, Godehard (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Levy, Mervyn (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Lister, Margot (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Lloyd, Davina (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Lloyd, Ward (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Lumumba, Patrice (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Lunt, James (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Maas, Jeremy (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Mackenzie, Sir Compton (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Mansfield, Kenneth (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Marsden, Philip (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Mellers, Wilfrid (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Melvill, Harold (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Middlemas, Keith (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Mollo, John (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Moncreiffe, Sir Iain (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Montgomery of Alamein -- Bernard Law Montgomery, 1st Viscount (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Morley-Fletcher, Hugo (Box 80)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Neal, W. Keith & D.H.L. Black (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Neame, L.E. (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Neuhaus, Heinrich (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Nickson, Hilda (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Noonan, Michael (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Norman, Herbert & John (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Oag, Shay (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Oliver, Paul (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Orga, Ates (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Osborn, Reuben (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Palaiseul, Jean (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Pitter, Ruth (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Pugh, Gordon (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Pulbrook, Susan, Lady & Rosamund Gould (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Pushkin, Aleksandr Sergeyevich (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Rawson, Philip S. (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Raynor, Henry (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Reitlinger, Gerald (Box 81)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Restif de la Bretonne, Nicolas Edme (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Ricjetts, Howard (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Rieth, Adolf (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Ringer, Vivian Barbara (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Robbins Landon, H.C. (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Robins, Eric (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Ross, Maggie (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Routh, Francis (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Rowland, Peter (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Sanders, Bruce (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Sandon, Henry (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Savage, George (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Schwarz, Boris (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Silverlight, John (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Skelton, Geoffrey (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Seipolt, Adalbert (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Snow, Peter (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Stasov, Vladimir (Box 82)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Storey, R.L. (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Summerson, Sir John Newenham (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Swain, Margaret Helen (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Taylerson, A.W.F. (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Tester, M.H. (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Thomson, David (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Turner book (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Twitchett, John & Betty Bailey (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Verlet, Pierre (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Victorian Collector series. (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Walker, Alan (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Walker, C.F. (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Wardle, Patricia (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Wenn, Leslie (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Werth, Alexander (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Wheatcroft, Harry (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Whiter, L.R. (Box 83)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Wickman, J.W. (Box 84)
    - Barrie & Jenkins: Williams, Neville (Box 84)